[
    {
        "question": "ويليام",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "نامي",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "لوفي",
        "response": "لوفي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ايرين",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "استا",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "همتارو",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "الويفيا",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "نويل",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "رايلي",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "ال",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "لاو",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "مادارا",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
